[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "And, Mark, it appears to me that the players are slowly starting to trickle back on the field, is that your assessment as you're looking?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "Mark", ",", "it", "appears", "to", "me", "that", "the", "players", "are", "slowly", "starting", "to", "trickle", "back", "on", "the", "field", ",", "is", "that", "your", "assessment", "as", "you", "'re", "looking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Yes, the official -- the ball sits at the 40 yard line.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "the", "official", "--", "the", "ball", "sits", "at", "the", "40", "yard", "line", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "Do you like what you see for maybe the second term Obama already?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "what", "you", "see", "for", "maybe", "the", "second", "term", "Obama", "already", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Oh, I love the man, I voted for him originally.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "love", "the", "man", ",", "I", "voted", "for", "him", "originally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "America needs to find other business models, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["America", "needs", "to", "find", "other", "business", "models", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Well, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Joe Carter?", "question_tokens": ["Joe", "Carter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Don, I can barely hear you, my man.", "answer_tokens": ["Don", ",", "I", "can", "barely", "hear", "you", ",", "my", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Carter"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "Ma'am?", "question_tokens": ["Ma'am", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "We've got a school shooting.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "got", "a", "school", "shooting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Chardon High School"]}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "What school?", "question_tokens": ["What", "school", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Chardon High School.", "answer_tokens": ["Chardon", "High", "School", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "UNIDENTIFIED 911 OPERATOR: Chardon High School?", "question_tokens": ["UNIDENTIFIED", "911", "OPERATOR", ":", "Chardon", "High", "School", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "CD", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Yes, ma'am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "ma'am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Chardon High School"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "RB", ":", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "The moment that you were shot what goes through your mind?", "question_tokens": ["The", "moment", "that", "you", "were", "shot", "what", "goes", "through", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "What I -- what I really -- what was going through my mind was I had to get out of the high school and really nothing else flows through your mind.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "--", "what", "I", "really", "--", "what", "was", "going", "through", "my", "mind", "was", "I", "had", "to", "get", "out", "of", "the", "high", "school", "and", "really", "nothing", "else", "flows", "through", "your", "mind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "How did you deal with it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "deal", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "I had a lot of support.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "a", "lot", "of", "support", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Did you despair?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "despair", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "I mean, I did, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "did", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Or what was it that they did that helped you?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "what", "was", "it", "that", "they", "did", "that", "helped", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Well, I had a lot of support from other people texting me and calling me that are in wheelchairs.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "had", "a", "lot", "of", "support", "from", "other", "people", "texting", "me", "and", "calling", "me", "that", "are", "in", "wheelchairs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "What was that like for you as his mother?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "like", "for", "you", "as", "his", "mother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": ".", "answer_tokens": ["."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "What is the prognosis they made?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "prognosis", "they", "made", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "They said that they were cautiously optimistic when they came out of surgery, but -- so we're still hoping and praying.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "said", "that", "they", "were", "cautiously", "optimistic", "when", "they", "came", "out", "of", "surgery", ",", "but", "--", "so", "we", "'re", "still", "hoping", "and", "praying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Very particular support group that knows exactly what you've been through?", "question_tokens": ["Very", "particular", "support", "group", "that", "knows", "exactly", "what", "you", "'ve", "been", "through", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Well, if somebody who's been through it but has an outlook that's positive.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "somebody", "who", "'s", "been", "through", "it", "but", "has", "an", "outlook", "that", "'s", "positive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "I would love that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "love", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Shake on it?", "question_tokens": ["Shake", "on", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Does that bring it all back?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "bring", "it", "all", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "But aside from that, have you set yourself things that you really want to achieve?", "question_tokens": ["But", "aside", "from", "that", ",", "have", "you", "set", "yourself", "things", "that", "you", "really", "want", "to", "achieve", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "Well, obviously, I had to -- I had to switch around my career a little bit that I was aiming for.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "obviously", ",", "I", "had", "to", "--", "I", "had", "to", "switch", "around", "my", "career", "a", "little", "bit", "that", "I", "was", "aiming", "for", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "What would you want to be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "want", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "I wanted to be just an electrician in the union and I don't believe that can happen practically right now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wanted", "to", "be", "just", "an", "electrician", "in", "the", "union", "and", "I", "do", "n't", "believe", "that", "can", "happen", "practically", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2011"]}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Before you met Tony, what was -- what was your life like?", "question_tokens": ["Before", "you", "met", "Tony", ",", "what", "was", "--", "what", "was", "your", "life", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "I was doing a lot of current therapies, you know, psychiatry, psychology, which I started in 2011.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "doing", "a", "lot", "of", "current", "therapies", ",", "you", "know", ",", "psychiatry", ",", "psychology", ",", "which", "I", "started", "in", "2011", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "Did it help, any of that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "it", "help", ",", "any", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "So you had -- why don't you tell him what your symptoms were at the time?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "had", "--", "why", "do", "n't", "you", "tell", "him", "what", "your", "symptoms", "were", "at", "the", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Basically insomnia.", "answer_tokens": ["Basically", "insomnia", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "What was the rock bottom moment for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "rock", "bottom", "moment", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "The rock bottom moment for me in a sense was -- it was after my second divorce, just being -- I pushed so many people away, couldn't figure out why I felt this way.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "rock", "bottom", "moment", "for", "me", "in", "a", "sense", "was", "--", "it", "was", "after", "my", "second", "divorce", ",", "just", "being", "--", "I", "pushed", "so", "many", "people", "away", ",", "could", "n't", "figure", "out", "why", "I", "felt", "this", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "What do you say in this situation?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "in", "this", "situation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Well, it's interesting, and we've done this with hundreds of wounded warriors and different soldiers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", ",", "and", "we", "'ve", "done", "this", "with", "hundreds", "of", "wounded", "warriors", "and", "different", "soldiers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "What advice would you give him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "advice", "would", "you", "give", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Well, basically, he has to take back his life.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "basically", ",", "he", "has", "to", "take", "back", "his", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "He built a small business to start with and one of those young women that worked for him was addicted to meth, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["He", "built", "a", "small", "business", "to", "start", "with", "and", "one", "of", "those", "young", "women", "that", "worked", "for", "him", "was", "addicted", "to", "meth", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Methamphetamine, right.", "answer_tokens": ["Methamphetamine", ",", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Why don't you share with him the story of how you end up in your new business?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "you", "share", "with", "him", "the", "story", "of", "how", "you", "end", "up", "in", "your", "new", "business", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "What was that like for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "like", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Or do you have a little bit of (INAUDIBLE), which is that ferocity of spirit?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "have", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", ",", "which", "is", "that", "ferocity", "of", "spirit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "I think ferocity of spirit is critical for everybody, but we all have it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "ferocity", "of", "spirit", "is", "critical", "for", "everybody", ",", "but", "we", "all", "have", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "ORGAN: Do we all have it?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Do", "we", "all", "have", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Yes, we do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "we", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "Is that a good focus to look at children, to look at other things and say, \"You know what, stop feeling sorry for myself; it's for him, for her, it's for that\"?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "good", "focus", "to", "look", "at", "children", ",", "to", "look", "at", "other", "things", "and", "say", ",", "``", "You", "know", "what", ",", "stop", "feeling", "sorry", "for", "myself", ";", "it", "'s", "for", "him", ",", "for", "her", ",", "it", "'s", "for", "that", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VB", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "''", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "Most of it -- I think what's really beautiful about most human beings is that we'll do more for others we love than we'll ever do for ourselves.", "answer_tokens": ["Most", "of", "it", "--", "I", "think", "what", "'s", "really", "beautiful", "about", "most", "human", "beings", "is", "that", "we", "'ll", "do", "more", "for", "others", "we", "love", "than", "we", "'ll", "ever", "do", "for", "ourselves", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "And Mike, what do you -- what do you say to these people suffering in America right now?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Mike", ",", "what", "do", "you", "--", "what", "do", "you", "say", "to", "these", "people", "suffering", "in", "America", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "I got to tell you, Tony is absolutely right.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "to", "tell", "you", ",", "Tony", "is", "absolutely", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "But actually all those emotions are just barriers to getting back on your feet, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["But", "actually", "all", "those", "emotions", "are", "just", "barriers", "to", "getting", "back", "on", "your", "feet", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "TO", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "That's correct.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130203pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "If I should (INAUDIBLE), you can have any one thing, you can have good health, you can have money, you can have the fame that allows you to inspire people, what would you choose as the one thing?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "should", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", ",", "you", "can", "have", "any", "one", "thing", ",", "you", "can", "have", "good", "health", ",", "you", "can", "have", "money", ",", "you", "can", "have", "the", "fame", "that", "allows", "you", "to", "inspire", "people", ",", "what", "would", "you", "choose", "as", "the", "one", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "Certainly I think without health, you're not around to do anything.", "answer_tokens": ["Certainly", "I", "think", "without", "health", ",", "you", "'re", "not", "around", "to", "do", "anything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]